<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Iravi | Celebrating Mothehood</title>
    <link>/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Iravi | Celebrating Mothehood</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:51:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pregnancy Nutrition</title>
      <link>/courses/pregnancy_nutrition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:51:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/pregnancy_nutrition/</guid>
      <description>During pregnancy, to nourish your body, you have to take nutritious foods with a well- balanced diet. Good nutrition helps you handle the extra demands on your body as your pregnancy progresses. To balance a healthy weight &amp;amp; remain active during pregnancy regular exercise is required. Diet Chart will be provided.
The session includes:  Diet &amp;amp; Nutrition Mindfulness Understand your body during pregnancy Exercise&amp;amp; Meditation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labor and Birth</title>
      <link>/courses/labor_and_birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:50:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/labor_and_birth/</guid>
      <description>This session will help pregnant women in overcoming their fear of birth. With all the right support &amp;amp; knowledge you can make your birth memorable.
The session includes:  Stages of Labor Pain management techniques Medical procedures Cesarean delivery Decision making  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newborn care</title>
      <link>/courses/newborn_care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:49:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/newborn_care/</guid>
      <description>The newborn care session for expectant parents helps to build confidence by better understanding the concepts in taking care of their babies during the early stage of parenting.
The session includes:  Newborn procedures Bathing Diapering Feeding pattern Sleeping pattern Baby cues Debunking the myths Newborn Warning signs  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postpartum care</title>
      <link>/courses/postpartum_care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:48:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/postpartum_care/</guid>
      <description>The postpartum care session deals with the guidance of woman wellness care in the early weeks of critical period after delivery.Anticipatory guidance should begin during pregnancy as the postpartum period is important for mother to recover physically &amp;amp; mentally. This session will help ease the transition into parenthood by identify your postpartum needs in advance and plan for how they’ll be met.
The session includes:  Physical recovery – Early &amp;amp; Later postpartum period Postpartum warning signs Postpartum mood disorders Caring for yourself Postpartum fitness  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breastfeeding</title>
      <link>/courses/breastfeeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:47:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/breastfeeding/</guid>
      <description>Breastfeeding is an innate ability within Mom &amp;amp; baby dyad. Though it is natural, it is really complex nowadays towards a successful breastfeeding journey.
To help you succeed in this process with right support &amp;amp; guidance, you will learn the following,  Golden hour after birth Latching positions &amp;amp; techniques How to boost up your milk supply Breastfeeding myths &amp;amp; facts Baby’s behavior &amp;amp; hunger cues Milk Expression &amp;amp; Storage  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prenatal Bonding</title>
      <link>/courses/prenatal_bonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:47:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/prenatal_bonding/</guid>
      <description>The Prenatal bonding is the establishment of bonding between mother and baby when the baby is in womb. Baby’s behavior depends upon the mental &amp;amp; emotional state of her mother during pregnancy. Prenatal bonding helps you to deliver a smart &amp;amp; healthy baby
The session includes:  Early Brain development Bonding techniques with the unborn baby Stimulation techniques Visualization  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
